Booth Tarkington Papers, 1812-1956 (bulk 1899-1946): Finding Aid C0062
Manuscripts Division
- Series 1: Writings, 1893-1986; 167 boxes
  - Subseries 1F: Film Scenarios, dates not examined; 4 boxes
    - Edgar Scenarios, dates not examined; 2 boxes
      - Edgar's Hamlet, 1926; 1 folder Signed autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 132, Folder 9)
      - Edgar's Jonah Day, 1926; 1 folder Signed autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 132, Folder 10)
      - Edgar's Little Sare: TMs (1926), 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 132, Folder 11)
      - Edgar's Sunday Courtship, undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 132, Folder 12)
      - Get Rich Quick Edgar, 1920; 1 folder Signed autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 132, Folder 13)
      - Edgar's Black Magic (not produced), undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 132, Folder 14)
      - Edgar's New Gog (not produced), undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 132, Folder 15)
      - Edgar Went Swimming (not produced), undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 133, Folder 1)
      - Edgar's Wonderful Father (not produced), undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 133, Folder 2)
      - Edgar's Surprise Package (not produced), undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 133, Folder 3)
      - Good Ole Snow (not produced), undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 133, Folder 4)
      - Edgar the Anti-Suffragist (not produced), undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 133, Folder 5)
      - Untitled, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 6)
      - Untitled, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 7)
      - Edgar Makes a Movie: Outline, (incomplete, not produced), undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 133, Folder 8)
      - Edgar Goes West: Outline, (incomplete, not produced), undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 133, Folder 8)
      - Notes Insertions, Letter to Mr. Buchanan, undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - A Great Man's Career (unproduced), undated; 2 folders Typed manuscript (Box 134, Folder 1-2)
    - Hardy Family Scenario, dates not examined; 1 box
      - Typed Manuscript and Letter, 1944; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 1)
      - Manuscript (not produced), undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 135, Folder 2)
      - Manuscript (not produced), 1944; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 3)
      - Jackass Smith: Manuscript (not produced), undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 135, Folder 4)
      - Jennie Grant (not produced), undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - The Millionaire, dates not examined; 1 box
      - Manuscript, 1931; 1 folder Typed manuscript, signed (Box 135, Folder 6)
      - Typed Manuscript, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Personality Plus or Prize Girl: Manuscript (unproduced), 1937; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Pied Piper Malone, 1924; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - The Wondering Jew (unproduced), undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - Will Rogers Sketch: Manuscript (never produced), undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 1G: Radio Scripts, dates not examined; 3 boxes
    Consists of manuscripts for radio scripts, including "Maud and Cousin Bill" (shows 1-100), "Let's Look Before We Leap," and "The New England Story I Like Best," as well as others.
    - Maud and Cousin Bill (Shows 1-40), 1932-1933; 5 folders Typed manuscript (Box 136, Folder 1-5)
    - Maud and Cousin Bill (Shows 41-100), 1932-1933; 7 folders Typed manuscript (Box 137, Folder 1-7)
    - On Blindness for the Better Vision Institute, 1939; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - On Conscription in Peacetime, 1945; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - "Cows are Like Money" (for the Treasury Dept.), 1945; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - "Facing the Year 1946": Studio Copy, 1945; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - "Fools Will Burn": Studio Copy, 1945; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - For The Indiana Committee for Victory, 1943; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - "The Help Each Other Club": Manuscript, 1933; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - "Lady Hamilton and Her Nelson": Manuscript, Proofs, 1940; 4 folders Typed manuscript (Box 138, Folder 8-11)
    - "Let's Look Before We Leap", 1945; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - On Maine, 1944; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - "The New England Story I Like Best", 1937; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - Obituary Tribute to Franklin D. Roosevelt: Manuscript, 1945; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 138, Folder 15)
    - Remarks Upon a Program of the Indianapolis Symphony Orchestra Broadcast on the NBC Radio Network, 1939; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 138, Folder 16)
    - Announcement for the Treasury Dept. 7th War Loan, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 17)
    - "Two Choices" (Script Supporting War Bonds), 1942; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 18)
      Includes manuscript and typed letters.
    - For the 6th War Loan Drive, 1944; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 138, Folder 19)
    - "Young Americans" (Script for Office of Civilian Defense), 1942; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 138, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 1H: Poems/Songs/Verses, 1896-1903; 1 box
    Consists of manuscripts of poems, songs, and verses, such as "The Assembly Coquette," "Lady Mehitabel (A Ballad in Four Colors)," and "Princeton Days," as well as others.
    - "Apart": Lyrics, 1903; 1 folder (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - "The Assembly Coquette", undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - "The Barons", 1897; 1 folder Typed manuscript, copy (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - "Chrismas, 1941", undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - "The Clemantis Garden", undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - "Coast Artillery": Manuscript, 1943; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Easter Thanks Offering, undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - "Fidelity", undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - "Just Because I'm Rich and Grand", undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript, copy (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - "Lady Mehitabel (A Ballad in Four Colors)", undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - "A Letter of Regrets": Manuscripts, Galley, Photostats in John-a-Dreams, 1896 September; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - "Love on the Skull": Manuscript, undated; 1 folder (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - "Lives Depending for this Meaning Upon Mr. Henry Parson's Remaining Seated", undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - "Mary Neal and Other Poems", undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - "Materialism": Manuscripts, Proof Sheet, undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - "My Lady With the Blue Dress On", undated; 2 folders Typed manuscript (Box 139, Folder 8-9)
    - "Quiatanon", undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - "O, Lady, Scorn Me!", undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - "Pink Statin": Manuscripts, Proof Sheet, undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - "Princeton Days" (Carmins Princetonia, The University Song Book), 1894; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - "The Proud Lover": A November Leaf, 1896; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - "The School Child", undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - "The Sleeping Duenna", undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - "Valentine": Manuscript, undated; 1 folder (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - "A Wolintine", undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 139, Folder 14)
    - "The Mandolin," "The August Night," "Firefly," "The Frog", 1897; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts, photocopy of newspaper (Box 139, Folder 15)
      Published under Broad Ripple in The Indianapolis Journal, 1897 August 1.
    - Untitled Verses in The Indianapolis Journal Under Nom de Plume "John Coberton", 1896-1897; 1 folder (Box 139, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Writings and Drawings, undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 1I: Operetta, undated; 1 box
    Consists of the manuscript for "The Songs Of Rappetin."
    - "The Songs Of Rappetin", undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 1J: Non-Fiction Books, 1923; 7 boxes
    Consists of the manuscripts for the nonfiction works "The Collector's Whatnot," "On Plays, Playwights and Playgoers," "Some Old Portraits," "The World Does Move," and "Your Amiable Uncle."
    - The Collector's Whatnot, 1923; 1 box
      - Autograph Manuscript, 1923; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - Drawings, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - On Plays, Playwights and Playgoers, dates not examined; 1 box
      - Galleys, Page Proofs, Collection of Booth Tarkington Correspondence, undated; 5 folders Typed manuscript (Box 142, Folder 1-5)
        Collection of correspondence published by Princeton University Library, 1959.
      - Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Some Old Portraits, 1939; 4 boxes
      - Manuscript, 1939; 6 folders Typed manscript (Box 143, Folder 1-6)
      - Manuscript, undated; 7 folders Typed manscript (Box 144, Folder 1-7)
      - Manuscript, undated; 8 folders Typed manscript (Box 145, Folder 1-8)
      - Galleys, Page Proofs, undated; 6 folders Typed manscript (Box 146, Folder 1-6)
    - The World Does Move: Manuscript, 1928; 7 folders Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 147, Folder 1-7)
    - Your Amiable Uncle: Revised Page Proofs, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 1K: Articles, dates not examined; 10 boxes
    Consists of manuscripts for articles written by Booth Tarkington.
    - A-D, dates not examined; 63 folders (Box 148, Folder 1-63)
    - E-I, dates not examined; 62 folders (Box 149, Folder 1-62)
    - J-P, dates not examined; 54 folders (Box 150, Folder 1-54)
    - R-T, dates not examined; 58 folders (Box 151, Folder 1-58)
    - U-W, dates not examined; 36 folders (Box 152, Folder 1-36)
    - Untitled, dates not examined; 12 folders (Box 153, Folder 1-12)
    - A-H, Oversize, dates not examined; 44 folders (Box 154, Folder 1-44)
    - I-N, Oversize, dates not examined; 28 folders (Box 155, Folder 1-28)
    - Q-V, Oversize, dates not examined; 25 folders (Box 156, Folder 1-25)
    - W-Untitled, Oversize, dates not examined; 10 folders (Box 157, Folder 1-10)
  - Subseries 1L: Speeches, dates not examined; 1 box
    Consists of manuscripts for speeches written and/or given by Booth Tarkington.
    - Speeches, undated; 23 folders (Box 158, Folder 1-23)
  - Subseries 1M: Art Notes, dates not examined; 1 box
    Consists of a catalogue of Tarkington's paintings as well as notes taken on art.
    - Catalogue of Tarkington's Paintings, undated; 1 folder (Box 159, Folder 1)
      Also includes some photos of same.
    - Condensed Catalogue of Some of the Seawood Pictures, undated; 2 folders (Box 159, Folder 2-3)
    - Art Notes, undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 1N: Juvenilia, dates not examined; 1 box
    Consists of juvenilia, including math problems, diaries, school copybooks, and drawings.
    - Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Drawings: Haverly-Tidd Reincarnation Comedy; "Memory" Poem, undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 160, Folder 2)
      Also includes outline of a play, and 2 untitled verses.
    - Cass's Posthumous Letter to `59, undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Pages from a Chemistry Notebook, undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Diary, undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Diary, undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Diary Insert, undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Essay on Emerson for Exeter, undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Fragment from a Letter (?), undated; 1 folder (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - "Little Portia" (Short Story, incomplete), undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Math Problems, undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Piece Written for John-a-Dreams, undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - School Copybook, undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - School Copybook with Unfinished Story, undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - "The Squire's Trip", undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 160, Folder 15)
    - Theme on Indian (Grade School), undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 160, Folder 16)
    - Theme on "Reading", undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript, signed (Box 160, Folder 17)
    - Things Written While at Purdue College, undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 160, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 1O: Miscellaneous Works, dates not examined; 3 boxes
    Consists of manuscripts for miscellaneous works, including incomplete plays, poems, and drawings.
    - Notes, dates not examined; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - "In the Chinmney Corner" (Play, incomplete), undated; 1 folder Autograph and typed manuscripts (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - "What Is It?" (play) incomplete: AMs, dates not examined; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Poems and Drawings, undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Poems, undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - "The Trees", undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscripts, some signed (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Poetry and Verse, undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Works of Unconfirmed Origin, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Bound Works, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 162)
    - Miscellaneous Bound Works, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 163)
  - Subseries 1P: Fragments/Notes/Unfinished/Untitled/Unidentified, dates not examined; 2 boxes
    Consists of manuscripts for fragments, unfinished, or unidentified works of Booth Tarkington.
    - Essay on Friendship (Fragment), undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - "Except Ye Become As Little Children", undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - "The Great American", undated; 1 folder Typed and autograph manuscripts (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - "Henry the Great": Manuscript, undated; 3 folders (Box 164, Folder 5-7)
    - "Paradise Children" (Fragment), undated; 1 folder Typed and autograph manuscripts (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - "The Superior Tom" (unfinifshed), undated; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Fragment, Notes, Untitled Short Stories, Unidentified Works, undated; 22 folders Typed and autograph manuscripts (Box 165, Folder 1-22)
- Series 2: Drawings, 1918; 1 box
  Consists of drawings of Booth Tarkington.
  - Drawings, 1918; 1 box (Box 166)
- Series 3: Correspondence, 1880-1952; 47 boxes
  Consists of the correspondence of Booth Tarkington from individuals such as Carl Brandt, John T. Jameson, Fred Kelly, and Warrack Wallace.
  This series is arranged into two subseries: From Tarkington, and To Tarkington.
  - Subseries 3A: From Tarkington, 1881-1952; 25 boxes
    Consists of letters written by Booth Tarkington to individuals such as Carl Brandt, John T. Jameson, Fred Kelly, and Warrack Wallace.
    Arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
    - A, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Brandt, Carl, of Brandt & Brandt, 1932-1937; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Brandt, Carl, 1938; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Brandt, Carl, 1939; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Brandt, Carl, 1940; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Brandt, Carl, 1941-1942; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Brandt, Carl, 1943-1943; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Brandt, Carl, 1945-1946; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - C, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Calkins, Dan, 1983-1944; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - Costain, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Currie, Barton, 1921-1924; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Currie, Barton, 1925-1927; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Currie, Barton, 1928-1945; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Daniels, Harrison (Dan), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - Doubleday, Russell & Doubleday, Nelson Doran & Co., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Farr, Dan, 1935-1945; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Fleisher, Sidney R, 1939-1941; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Freedman, Harold, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Gordon, Ruth, 1926-1945; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - H, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Hale, Robert, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Hanson, D. P., 1932-1942; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Hawkins, Gaylord, 1910-1917; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - I, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - J, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Jackson, Basil R, 1943-1945; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 14)
    - Jackson, Malcolm, 1939-1944; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 15)
    - Jameson, Booth (nephew), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Jameson, John T. (nephew), 1899-1934; 1 folder (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Jameson, John T., 1937; 1 folder (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Jameson, John T., 1938; 1 folder (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Jameson, John T., 1939; 1 folder (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Jameson, John T., 1940; 1 folder (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Jameson, John T., 1941; 1 folder (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Jameson, John T., 1942; 1 folder (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Jameson, John T., 1943; 1 folder (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Jameson, John T., 1944; 1 folder (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Jameson, John T., 1945; 1 folder (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Jameson, John T., Donald B., & Booth T. (nephews): Letters from Europe, 1903-1906; 1 folder (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Jameson, John T. Jr., 1938-1945; 1 folder (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Jameson, Mrs. Ovid Butler (Haute) (sister), 1887-1899; 1 folder (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Jameson, Mrs. Ovid Butler, 1902-1909; 1 folder (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Jameson, Mrs. Ovid Butler, 1902-1909; 1 folder (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Jameson, Mrs. Ovid Butler, 1917-1922; 1 folder (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Jameson, Mrs. Ovid Butler, 1923-1928; 1 folder (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Jameson, Mrs. Ovid Butler, 1931-1933; 1 folder (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Jameson, Mrs. Ovid Butler, 1934-1936; 1 folder (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Kahler, Hugh MacNair, 1919-1924; 1 folder (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Kahler, Hugh MacNair, 1925-1929; 1 folder (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Kahler, Hugh MacNair, 1930-1937; 1 folder (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Kahler, Hugh MacNair, 1938-1942; 1 folder (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Kahler, Hugh MacNair, 1943-1946; 1 folder (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Kelly, Gregory, 1921-1923; 1 folder (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - Kelly, Fred, 1923-1937; 1 folder (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Kelly, Fred, 1939; 1 folder (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Kelly, Fred, 1940; 1 folder (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Kelly, Fred, 1941; 1 folder (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Kelly, Fred, 1942; 1 folder (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Kelly, Fred, 1943; 1 folder (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Kelly, Fred, 1944; 1 folder (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Kelly, Fred, 1945; 1 folder (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Kelly, Fred, undated; 1 folder (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Ludlow, Louis (House of Representatives), 1933-1945; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - M, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - McCulloch, Dr. Carl, 1911-1925; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - McCulloch, Dr. Carl, 1926-1937; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - McCulloch, Dr. Carl, 1938; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - McCulloch, Dr. Carl, 1939; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - McCulloch, Dr. Carl, 1940; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - McCulloch, Dr. Carl, 1941-1943; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - McCulloch, Dr. Carl, 1944; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - McCulloch, Dr. Carl, 1945-1946; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Murchison, Mrs. Kenneth, 1911-1912; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Murray, H. G. ("Big"), 1903-1942; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - N, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Neal, Adelaide, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Neall, Adelaide, 1940-1942; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - P, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Panofsky, Dr. Erwin, 1938-1952; 1 folder (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Roberts, Kenneth, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - S, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Silberman, David, 1933; 1 folder (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Silberman, David, 1934; 1 folder (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Silberman, David, 1935; 1 folder (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Silberman, David, 1936; 1 folder (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Silberman, David, 1937; 1 folder (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - Silberman, David, 1938; 1 folder (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Silberman, David, 1939; 1 folder (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Silberman, David, 1940; 1 folder (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Silberman, David, 1940; 1 folder (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Silberman, David, 1941; 1 folder (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Silberman, David, 1942; 1 folder (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - Silberman, David, 1943; 1 folder (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Silberman, David, 1944; 1 folder (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Silberman, David, 1945; 1 folder (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Henry Pratt, 1940-1946; 1 folder (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1914; 1 folder (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1915; 1 folder (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1906-1913; 1 folder (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1916; 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1917; 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1918; 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1919; 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1920; 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1921; 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1922; 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1923; 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1924-1929; 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1930-1934; 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1935-1936; 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1937-1939; 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1940; 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1941; 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1942; 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1943; 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 8)